<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--

    Copyright (c) 2024, 2026 TNO-ESI

    This program and the accompanying materials are made
    available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License 2.0
    which is available at https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-2.0/

    SPDX-License-Identifier: EPL-2.0

-->
<feature
      id="nl.esi.xplus.ui.feature"
      label="XPlus DSLs"
      version="4.2.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="TNO-ESI">

   <description>
      This feature includes XPlus Core languages feature and adds the default XPlus project language and help.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2018-2020, Embedded Systems Innovation by TNO.
All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      Copyright (c) 2018, Embedded Systems Innovation by TNO. All rights reserved.
 
Use of this software in binary form, without modification and without
redistribution, is permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
 
1. All advertising materials mentioning features or use of this software
    must display the following acknowledgement: This product includes
    software developed by Embedded Systems Innovation by TNO.
 
2. Neither the name of Embedded Systems Innovation by TNO nor the
    names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products
    derived from this software without specific prior written permission.
 
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY Embedded Systems Innovations by TNO &apos;&apos;AS IS&apos;&apos;
AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL Embedded Systems Innovations by
TNO BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT
OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR
BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY,
WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR
OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

This product includes software developed by the Electronic Systems Group at
the Department of Electrical Engineering of Eindhoven University of Technology.
   </license>

   <includes
         id="nl.esi.xplus.core.feature"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <requires>
      <import feature="net.sourceforge.plantuml.feature" version="1.1.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="nl.esi.xtext.actions.ui"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="nl.esi.xtext.expressions.ui"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="nl.esi.xtext.types.ui"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="nl.esi.xplus.doc.design"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
